{
  "subject": "Aptitude Test",
  "year": 2020,
  "quiz": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Select the correct answer: (a) 0.50 (b) 1.25 (c) 1.50 (d) 2.50 (e) 3.25",
      "options": {
        "A": "0.50",
        "B": "1.25",
        "C": "1.50",
        "D": "2.50",
        "E": "3.25"
      },
      "correct": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which number comes next? (a) 9 (b) 7 (c) 5 (d) 4 (e) 2",
      "options": {
        "A": "9",
        "B": "7",
        "C": "5",
        "D": "4",
        "E": "2"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Select the correct answer: (a) 8 (b) 5 (c) 2 (d) 1 (e) 0",
      "options": {
        "A": "8",
        "B": "5",
        "C": "2",
        "D": "1",
        "E": "0"
      },
      "correct": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "Which town has the largest iron and steel industry in Nigeria?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Ajaokuta",
        "B": "Aladja",
        "C": "Jos",
        "D": "Katsina",
        "E": "Oshogbo"
      },
      "correct": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "How many faces does a cube have?",
      "options": {
        "A": "3",
        "B": "4",
        "C": "5",
        "D": "6",
        "E": "7"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "Which of the following converts electrical energy to heat energy?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Air conditioner",
        "B": "Ceiling fan",
        "C": "Loudspeaker",
        "D": "Pressing iron",
        "E": "Television set"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Arrange the following in ascending order: Hamlet, village, city, town.",
      "options": {
        "A": "city, town, village, hamlet",
        "B": "hamlet, city, town, village",
        "C": "hamlet, village, town, city",
        "D": "town, village, city, hamlet",
        "E": "village, hamlet, city, town"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Bus and road : Train and .........",
      "options": {
        "A": "pathway",
        "B": "rail",
        "C": "runways",
        "D": "station",
        "E": "waterways"
      },
      "correct": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "ANIMAL in code",
      "options": {
        "A": "l\\zmrzo",
        "B": "ozmrzn",
        "C": "zmrnzo",
        "D": "zrmzno",
        "E": "znrmoz"
      },
      "correct": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "SAVE is coded 8296. How would VASE be coded?",
      "options": {
        "A": "9268",
        "B": "8629",
        "C": "9826",
        "D": "9628",
        "E": "9286"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "\"John is my sister's son. John and I are related.\" Who is John?",
      "options": {
        "A": "I and John's father",
        "B": "John is my brother",
        "C": "John is my cousin",
        "D": "John is my nephew",
        "E": "John is my step brother"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "Choose the word that pairs with 'gun'.",
      "options": {
        "A": "king",
        "B": "tailor",
        "C": "driver",
        "D": "hunter",
        "E": "none"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    }
  ]
}
